(Amy:)This is so exciting.
(Amy:)Soon my upper lip will be the same
fake-blond as my beautiful best friend.
Hey, this is my natural hair color.
(Raj:)Now.
(Penny:)So does Sheldon have anything special
planned for you tomorrow night?
(Amy:)Yes. According to the relationship agreement,
on the anniversary of our first date...
(Amy:)...he must take me to a nice dinner,
ask about my day...
(Amy:)...and engage in casual physical contact...
(Amy:)...that a disinterested onlooker
might mistake for intimacy.
(Penny:)That's hot.
(Penny:)You kids better use protection.
- How long does this stay on?
- Just a couple minutes.
(Penny:)- You've really never done this before?
- Once in high school. But I dozed off...
...and woke up with second degree
chemical burns on my face.
(Penny:)Oh, my gosh, that's awful.
Did the other kids make fun of you?